

Nguyen Ngoc Anh Thu

Frontend Developer

Objective

I am willing to seek a working chance in a professional environment where I can utilize my skills, knowledge, and passion to contribute to the company's success while gaining valuable experience and further enhancing my professional growth.

Education

Information Technology, University of Science (HCMUS)

Bachelor's Degree: 2021 - 2024

GPA: 8.6/10

Projects

Taxi Booking App

- Our Taxi Booking project is designed for both mobile and web platforms, including real-time booking, driver tracking, multi-platform accessibility, booking history and notification system
- Number of members: 4
- Position: Front-end developer for web application
- Technology in use (Front-end): HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap v5, Ant Design, Material UI, ReactJS, Redux, Google Maps API, Leaflet, i18n, Socket IO
- Source code: https://github.com/AnhThu0109/grabWebApp
- Video demo: *Link*

Account Management

- A web application provides a secure login system with different user roles (admin and normal), responsive design for various devices and features such as user registeration, user dashboard, user information and so on.
- Number of members: 1

Details0797038003
Binh Duong Province

Skills
HTML
CSS
JavaScript
Bootstrap v
Ant Design
Material U
ReactJS
NextJS
Redux

Languages
English (IELTS 6.0)

- Technology in use: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap v5, Ant Design, ReactJS, Redux
- Source code: https://github.com/AnhThu0109/UserManagement

Movie Web

- A web application offers users a seamless and visually appealing experience to explore and discover their favorite movies (inspired from website https://www.themoviedb.org).
- Number of members: 1
- Technology in use: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap v5, Ant Design, Material UI, ReactJS, Redux
- Source code: https://github.com/AnhThu0109/moviesapp

Human Resource Management, Shinhan DS Vietnam

- A web application provided management solution for HR Department at ShinhanDS Vietnam using ReactJS.
- Position: Front-end developer

SOL Cambodia Mobile Application, Shinhan DS Vietnam

- A mobile application for financial services of Shinhan Cambodia bank using Javascript ES6 in Websquare5 studio.
- Position: Front-end developer

Work Experience

Software Developer, Shinhan DS Vietnam, Ho Chi Minh city

DECEMBER 2022 - AUGUST 2023

- Join in developing HRM web application using ReactJS.
- Join in developing banking app for Shinhan Cambodia using Javascript ES6 in Websquare5 studio.

Achivements

Certificate of "12 Weeks to Master Front-end ReactJS", LikeLion

SEPTEMBER 2022 - FEBRUARY 2023